Chinu Bala Dash

chinubala 1995@gmail.com 9348296073 bhubaneswar, odisha

Summary

Looking for a full time position in the software development, where I can enhance my knowledge and give my effort towards the success of the organization. i am having experience in web development with 2 year 8 months of experience in HTML, CSS, JS, React js, Redux toolkit PHP, Material UI, AG Grid, Bootstrap.

Experience

Software Developer

Muvi entertainment pvt ltd. • bhubaneswar, odisha 07/2021 - 12/2022

Muvi is the World's only All-in-One OTT Platform which allows you to launch White Label Multi-Device Video Streaming Platform

offering Video on Demand (VOD) & Live Streaming as well as Audio Streaming Platform offering Music Streaming and Live Audio

Broadcast instantly! Muvi includes everything, fully managed, end-to-end, all controlled from single CMS, no coding or IT teams required.

- Worked with team of 12 member and provided end to end solution for clients
- Working on 1 project which is Tattle for which first client is Turning Stone , NY , USA , gradually we are increasing customer for it
- and we are also using it internally in our company.
- Tattle basically convert your conversations over email, phone, chat, and web request to tickets in one tap. Tattle allows you to
- create, assign, track, update ticket details on one interface thereby promoting a collaborative workflow while increasing agent
- productivity. Stay on top of each ticket with a bird's-eye view of dependencies, bottle-necks, response time, resolution time,
- individual performance and more.
- What Tattle offers and others dont is :-
- Faster Integration across wider platforms
- Unlimited Customization Support
- Customizable User-friendly UI
- · Stronger Security with auto-reporting of unauthorized access
- Easy Data Migration
- White Glove Support
- · working under my manager and my Team Lead

Internship Program

Mythical Phoenix • bhubaneswar, odisha

11/2020 - 04/2021

- Faster Integration across wider platforms
- Unlimited Customization Support
- · Customizable User-friendly UI
- Stronger Security with auto-reporting of unauthorized access
- Easy Data Migration
- White Glove Support
- Responsibities
- · working under my manager and my Team Lead

Skills

ReactJS, Redux Toolkit, Redux Thunk, HTML 5, CSS3, Material ui, Next JS, Ant, antd, Bootstrap, PHP, YII, Git, BITBUCKET

Education

Bachelor Of Computer Application

Utkal University • bhubaneswar, odisha 09/2013 - 08/2016

Master Of Computer Application

Utkal University • bhubaneswar, odisha 09/2016 - 10/2019